

# Luis Felipe Rochinski Rodrigues

luisfeliperochinskirodrigues@gmail.com | +55 42 99156 3583 | 26 years old

luisfeliperochinskirodrigues.github.io | linkedin.com/me

Ponta Grossa – Paraná - Brazil

I have advanced experience in IT infrastructure and user support, an area that I have been working on for several years optimizing experience and knowledge. My last experience is the management of energy efficiency projects, searching for possibilities and improvements to steam piping system, and energy consumption from any kind. I'm working on my knowledge about electricity infrastructure and smart controlling of machines to do a better work and improve my capabilities.

# PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

Management of energy efficiency projects, analysis to find improvements, analysis from machines and sensors, analysis of efficiency production, analysis report, AutoCAD, DevOps, IT infrastructure, knowledge about IoT, MS Office.

### SKILLS

Software: PCB Design Proteus, PCB Eagle, NI Multisim, Autodesk AutoCAD, HTML5, CSS3, MS Office, Corel Draw.

Programming Languages & Features: JS | Frameworks: Node, Tailwind, Vue.js.

Languages: Portuguese, Advanced English, Basic Spanish.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **Electrical Technician | Continental – 06/2023**

 Management and implementation of energy efficiency projects, analysis from data values, documentation and management of steam and electricity consumption, analysis to search improvements, management of sensors from machines, controlling supervisory, data improvements, electrical documentation.

# **Engineering Analyst Intern | Continental** – 10/2022 to 06/2023

 Study of energy efficiency projects, analysis from data values, documentation and management of steam and energy consumption, analysis to search improvements.

## IT Analyst | Self-Employed - 10/2021 to 10/2022

 Provision of network infrastructure services and support of servers for companies, Assistance to Users of RDP, maintenance and management of IT infrastructure and implementation of auxiliary systems.

# **Trainee in IT & Electronic | Klop Informática -** 08/2019 to 04/2020

 Support and service in business IT, maintenance of electronic power peripherals (motherboards and nobreaks).

### **EDUCATION**

**Ponta Grossa Educational College - Anhanguera** Graduate: Bachelor of Electrical Engineering - 2019-2023.

**Federal Technological University of Paraná** – **UTFPR** Studied: Bachelor of Electronical Engineering - 2016-2019.

**Technological innovation Project: UTFPR – PG / IUT** Research: Creation and development of electronic project.

Intellectual Property: [2] Henrique Terzi Lucchetta / [1] Luis Felipe Rochinski Rodrigues. From: 13/04/2017 to 23/07/2020.

### Extension Project: UTFORCE E-RACING - UTFPR

Research: Design engineering / development of 3D encapsulation for telemetry sensors, and sensor development for electric vehicle suspension. Supervisor: Professor Frederik Conrad Jensen. From: 07/08/2018 to 07/08/20

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Microsoft Office
- Hardware Maintenance
- Methodology and Analysis and Problem Solving
- Business Plan and Feasibility Analysis Management
- Business Strategy
- Entrepreneurial Profile
- Entrepreneurship
- Business Model and Canvas
- Design Thinking
- Microsoft Windows Server 2019